このReadmeには、同時にダウンロードされたデータの使い方について、データを作成した人のお願いが書いてあります。 
新たにダウンロードした場合、お願いが変わっていることがありますので、新たにダウンロードしたデータに付属のReadmeを必ず読み直してください。 
非営利の使用であり、公序良俗や、関係する方々に迷惑をかけない限り

•データを自分の責任で改造して使ってもかまいません。
•自分で責任をとれる限り、改造したデータは配布してかまいません。元データの再配布はご遠慮ください。 
•ただし配布する場合、必ず同じ条件（非営利・改造可・改造データ再配布可）で、改造の履歴を記述して配布してください。
•暴力自体を目的とする動画、直接的な猥褻行為を目的とする動画、他人を中傷する動画には使用しないでください。
•営利目的で使用される場合は下記までご連絡ください。

あひる@anatroccolo
mail:lilycage@mail.goo.ne.jp
twitter:anatroccolo_mmd


MY WISHES

This readme is only applicable to the model/accessory/motion data that you downloaded at the same time. 
When you download a newer version, you must read carefully the readme distributed with that newer version.

Only for noncommercial use, in respect for the right of all concerned and within the common courtesy, you may 

•NOT USE the model/accessory/motion data to videos with scenes of violence, sexual material or slander (such as R-rated)
•MODIFY the model/accessory/motion data at your own risk and on your own responsibility 
•REDISTRIBUTE ONLY the MODIFIED model/accessory/motion data (NEVER the original) UNDER THE SAME CONDITIONS of this readme, with the history of modifications, at your own risk and on your own responsibility.
•CONTACT ME, when you use for commercial.
JUST IMAGINE all creators behind the data you downloaded, and let’s enjoy OUR happy creative life. 

Anatroccolo
mail:lilycage@mail.goo.ne.jp
twitter:anatroccolo_mmd
